Contact

kbour806@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kevinbourque-rn-bsn-emba-89500864 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Hospitals Nursing

Kevin Bourque RN BSN EMBA

Travel RN for AYA Healthcarae ICU at Carrollton, Texas Cypress, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Electronic Medical Record (EMR), Nursing, Inpatient Care, Critical Care Nursing, Management, Clinical Research, and Customer Service. Strong operations professional graduated from Texas Woman's University Health Science Center Houston Texas. University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston.

Experience

Aya Healthcare
11 months

Travel RN for AYA Healthcarae ICU April 2020 - Present (3 months) Carrollton, Texas, United States

Staff nurse in ICU taking care of Covid-19 Patients and ICU patients

Travel RN for AYA Healthcare Pre-Op, PACU, and ICU February 2020 - April 2020 (3 months)

Los Alamos, New Mexico, United States

Travel RN for AYA Healthcare Pre-Op, PACU, and ICU August 2019 - February 2020 (7 months)

Kerrville, Texas, United States

Staff nurse in Pre-Op and PACU.

Memoral Hermann USPI Greater Heights Surgery Center Pre-Assessment/Preo-Op/PACU Clinical Manager April 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 5 months)

Houston, Texas

Memorial Hermann/West Houston Surgicare RN BSN Charge Nurse Pre-Op/PAT August 2015 - April 2018 (2 years 9 months)

970 Cambell Rd Houston Tx

Charge Nurse Pre-Op / PAT Safety Officer

Houston Metro Ortho & Spine Surgical Center Pre-Op/PACU RN Charge Nurse May 2013 - February 2015 (1 year 10 months) Charge Nurse

Memorial Hermann Katy
Clinical Manager for Day Surgery/Endo/Out Pt IV Infusion/Out Pt
Wound Care
July 2008 - November 2013 (5 years 5 months)

North Cypress Medical Center RN May 2007 - May 2013 (6 years 1 month) Cypress, Texas

Education

ICU STAFF NURSE

Texas Woman's University Health Science Center Houston Texas EMBA, Business Administration and Management, General · (2015 - 2016)

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston Nursing · (2007 - 2008)

Amarillo College

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1981 - 1988)